Guide to the W. Keith Kennedy papers, 1971-1978.
Kennedy, W. Keith papers, 1971-1978.
- Native Americans, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 67)
- Board of Natural Resource Organizations, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 68)
- Nematode, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 69)
- New York Farm Bureau, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 70)
- New York State Agricultural Association, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 71)
- New York State Agricultural Society, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 72)
- New York State Association of County Agricultural Agents (NYSACAA), 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 73)
- New York State Bankers Association, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 74)
- New York State Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 75)
- New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 76)
- New York Farmers, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 77)
- New York Farmers Award, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 78)
- New York Farm Electrification Council, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 79)
- New York State Food Processors, Inc., 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 80)
- New York State Forest Practice Board, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 81)
- New York State Grange, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 82)
- New York State Horticultural Society, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 83)
- Northeastern Regional Center for Rural Development, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 84)
- Northern New York, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 85)
- National Science Foundation (NSF), 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 86)
- Graduate School of Nutrition, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 87-88)
- Correspondence--O, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 89)
- Off-Campus Installations, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 90)
- Ombudsman, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 91)
- Oneida-Herkimer Counties, Planning for Local Development, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Operation Hitchhike, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Oral History, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Student Orientation, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Ornithology Laboratory, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA), 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Correspondence--P, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Payroll, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Personnel, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Pesticides, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 10-11)
- Pesticide Association of New York State (PANYS), 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Foundation Potato Seed Farm, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Pre-medical Advisory Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Presidential Appointments, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Professional Positions, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Professor at Large, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Promotions, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Proposal for State Agricultural Policy Commission, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Purchasing, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Correspondence--R, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Recycling, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Regents External Degrees, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Regents Tentative Statewide Plan for the Development of Post-Secondary Education, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Office of the Registrar, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Research Foundation of SUNY, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Rockefeller Foundation, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 27-28)
- Rural Development, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 29-32)
- Rural Development and Small Farm Research in Education, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Rural Poverty, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Rural Rehabilitation, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Correspondence--S, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Safety Division, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Safety, Rural Safety Council, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Scholar Incentive Awards, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Salaries, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Scholarships, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Schubmehl, Judi, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Science, Technology, and Society (STS), 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Self-help Housing, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Serving the People, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 45)
- Shackelton Point, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 46)
- Sheep Endowment Fund, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 47)
- Sloan Foundation, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 48)
- Statutory Management Information System (SMIS), 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 49)
- Sociology, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 50)
- Soil Conservation Service, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 51)
- SPICE, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 52)
- Office of Sponsored Research, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 53)
- State Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 54)
- Stipends, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 55)
- Dean of Students (Meyer, Elmer), 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 56)
- Student Employment, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 57)
- Student Information System (SIS), 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 58)
- Student Loan Program, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 59)
- Student Records and Finance Office, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 60)
- Student Records (Releasing of), 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 61)
- Summer Session, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 62)
- Correspondence--T, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 63)
- Teaching Assistants (TAs), 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 64)
- Joint Legislative Committee on Taylor Law, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 65)
- Teaching Loads, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 66)
- Tenure and Degrees of Faculty, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 67)
- Tissue Culture, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 68)
- Professional Titles, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 69)
- Toward the Year '85, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 70)
- Traffic Bureau, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 71)
- Cornell Travel Office, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 72)
- Tuition, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 73)
- Tuition Scholarship Plan, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 74)
- Turfgrass Research, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 75)
- Uihlein, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 76)
- University Relations, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 77)
- University Senate, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 78)
- University of the Philippines, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 79)
- United States Department of Agriculture (USDA), 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 80)
- Correspondence--V, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 81)
- Veterinary College, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 82)
- Virus Research Institute, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 83)
- Correspondence--W, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 84)
- Water Management Planning Unit, DEC, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 85)
- Water Resources, C.U., 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 86-87)
- Wayne County, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 88-89)
- Assembly Ways and Means Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 90)
- Weed Extension Program, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 91)
- Correspondence--X, Y, and Z, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 92)
- Traveling Fellowships, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 1-3)
- Traveling Fellowships, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 4-6)
- Traveling Fellowships, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
- Traveling Fellowship Instructors--Stencil, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Traveling Fellowships, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Traveling Fellowships, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Traveling Fellowships, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 12-13)
- Traveling Fellowships, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 14-15)
- Traveling Fellowships, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 16-17)
- Traveling Fellowships, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Traveling Fellowships, 1959-1964 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Traveling Fellowships, 1950-1955 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Farm Electrification Council--Executive Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Farm Electrification Council Conference, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Farm Electrification Council Conference, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Farm Electrification Council, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- New York Farmer Award, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- New York Farmer Award, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- New York Farmer Award, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- New York Farmer Award, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- New York Farmer Award, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- New York State Commission for Preservation of Agricultural Lands (Libby, Larry and Ditch, Ruth), 1966 (Box 9, Folder 30-31)
- Assistant to the President (Barlow, J. R.), 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Board of Trustees, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Controller and Treasurer (Peterson, Arthur H.), 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Counsel, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Dean of the Faculty (Penney, Norman), 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- President's Office, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Provost (Cooke, W. D.), 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- State Relations Coordinator (Tobin, Tom), 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Vice President for Administration (Lawrence, Samuel A.), 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Vice President for Campus Affairs (Gurowitz, William D.), 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Vice President for Planning (Mackesey, Thomas), 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- Vice President for Research (Cooke, W. D.), 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Vice Provost (Barlow, Mark Jr.), 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Vice Provost (McKeegan, Paul), 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Vice Provost (Risley, Robert F.), 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 46-47)
- Deans and Directors (D & D) Agendas, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 48)
- D & D Minutes, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 49-50)
- Travel Schedules, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 51)
- Committee of Chairmen, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 52)
- Statutory Deans' Meeting, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 53)
- Dean's Council, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 54-56)
- Department Heads' Meetings, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 57)
- Statutory Deans, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 58)
- SUNY--Board of Trustees, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 59-61)
- SUNY--Board of Trustees, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
- SUNY--Director of Budgets (Anslow, William), 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- SUNY--Campus Development, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 4-5)
- SUNY--Campus Liaison (Block, Murray), 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- SUNY--Campus Relations, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- SUNY--Chancellor (Boyer, Ernest L.), 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- SUNY--Conference of Presidents, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- SUNY--Consortia Membership, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- SUNY--Cornell Relations, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- SUNY--Council of Presidents, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 12-17)
- SUNY--Deputy Vice Chancellor (Ertell, Merton W.), 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- SUNY--Enrollments, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- SUNY--Executive Vice Chancellor (Kelly, James F.), 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- SUNY--Faculty Grants, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- SUNY--Faculty Senate, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- SUNY--Graduate Council (Murray, Daniel H.), 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- SUNY--Institute for Public Policy Alternatives, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- SUNY--International Programs, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- SUNY--Legislative Relations, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- SUNY--Newsletters, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- SUNY--Policy and Planning (Ingler, Charles), 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- SUNY--Presidents' Meetings, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- SUNY--Presidential Review Progress, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- SUNY--Provost for Undergraduate Education (Radley, Dr. Virginia L.), 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- SUNY--Special Projects, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- SUNY--Tuition, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- SUNY--Vice Chancellor for Academic Programs (Dearing, Bruce), 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- SUNY--Vice Chancellor for Finance, Management, and Business (Spindler, Harry), 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- SUNY--Vice Chancellor for Personnel and Employee Relations (MacKenzie, Kenneth), 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- SUNY--Vice Chancellor for University Affairs, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- SUNY--University-Wide Services and Special Programs, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- SUNY--Albany, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- SUNY--Brockport, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 40)
- SUNY--Buffalo, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 41)
- SUNY--Corning Community College, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 42)
- SUNY--Empire State College, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 43)
- SUNY--Genesee Community College, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 44)
- SUNY--Oswego, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- SUNY--Plattsburgh, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 46)
- SUNY--Agricultural and Technical (Ag & Tech) Presidents, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 47)
- SUNY--Ag & Tech--Cobleskill, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 48)
- SUNY--Ag & Tech--Delhi, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 49)
- SUNY--Ag & Tech--Farmingdale, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 50)
- SUNY--Ag & Tech--Morrisville, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 51)
- SUNY--Ag & Tech Transfer Students, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 52)
- Circular Letters (Kennedy, W. K.), 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 53)
- Circular Letters (Kent, G. C.), 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 54)
- Circular Letters (Spencer, James W.), 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 55)
- Chairmen Reviews, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 56)
- Assistant to the Dean (Kennedy, Laing), 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 57)
- Coordinator of Planning (Kent, G. C.), 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 58)
- Associate Dean (Spencer, James W.), 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 59)
- Liberty Hyde Bailey Professorship (Palm, Charles E.), 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 60)
- Agricultural Economics, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 61-65)
- Agricultural Economics Bulletins, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 66-67)
- Agricultural Engineering, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 68-70)
- Agronomy, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 71-74)
- Animal Sciences, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 1-5)
- Bailey Hortorium, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Communication Arts, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Ward, Professor William B., 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Education, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Entomology, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 17-Oct)
- Pesticide Residue Lab, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Cooperative Extension, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 19-21)
- County Agents, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- 4-H, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Cooperative Extension Advisory Council, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Regional and Specialized Agents, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Statewide Extension Work Planned Compared to Work Reported, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Finance and Business Office, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 28-29)
- Landscape Architecture, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Food Science, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 31-32)
- Institute of Food Science, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Geneva Open House, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- International Agricultural Development (IAD), 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 35-38)
- IAD Advisory Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- Turk, Dr. Retirement Dinner. Retirement Dinner, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- Library, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 41)
- Natural Resources, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 42-44)
- Arnot Forest, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 45)
- Youngs, William D. (Natural Resources), 1974 (Box 11, Folder 46)
- Plant Breeding, 1943-1974 (Box 11, Folder 47)
- Biometrics Unit, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 48)
- Plant Pathology, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 49)
- Dimock Lab Dedication, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 50)
- Pomology, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 51-52)
- Poultry, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
- Schano, Edward (Poultry), 1974 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Research, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Research Efforts--Agronomy, Milk, Poultry and Apples and Potatoes, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Resident Instruction, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 6-8)
- Rural Sociology, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 10-Sep)
- Vegetable Crops, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Long Island Vegetable Research Laboratory, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Biological Sciences (O'Brien, R.D.), 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 13-14)
- Biological Sciences--Accessory Instruction, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Biological Sciences--Executive Committee Meetings, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Biochemistry, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Cell Lab, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Ecology, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Genetics, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Microbiology, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Neurobiology, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Wiegand Herbarium, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Correspondence--A, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Office of Academic Funding, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Accessory Instruction, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Accounts, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Accounts In Overdraft, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Admissions, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Adjunct Professors, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Affirmative Action, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Agribusiness Council, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Agriculture Council of America, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Agricultural Affiliates, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Agricultural Leaders' Forum, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 35-36)
- Agricultural Resource Commission, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Agricultural Fund, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 38-40)
- Agricultural and Life Sciences Fund Advisory Council, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- New York State Department of Agriculture and Markets, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- Agri-Systems, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 43)
- Agway, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 44)
- Alumni Affairs, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 45)
- Alumni Association--College of Agriculture and Life Sciences, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 46)
- Alumni University, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 47)
- American Agriculturist, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 48)
- American Society of Agronomy, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 49)
- Anatomy--Physiology, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 50)
- Apple Growers Association, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 51)
- Aquaculture, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 52)
- College of Architecture, Art, and Planning, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 53)
- College of Arts and Science, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 54)
- Athletic Department, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 55)
- Correspondence--B, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 56)
- Bankhead Jones, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 57)
- Biophysics, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 58)
- Blood Donor Program, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 59)
- Breakebeen Project, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 60)
- Brigham Young Proposal, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 61)
- Budget--Cornell University, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 62)
- Division of the Budget, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 63)
- Buildings and Properties, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 64)
- Correspondence--C, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 65)
- Calendar, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 66)
- Carlson, Peter (Brookhaven), 1974 (Box 12, Folder 67)
- Council for Agricultural Society and Technology (CAST), 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 68)
- Catskills, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 69)
- Agricultural Census, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 70)
- Center for Environmental Quality Management (CEQM), 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 1-3)
- Chaplans, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Chenango, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Chronicle, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- City University, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Computers, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Conferences, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Cornell Plantations, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Communication Specialists for Population Affairs (COSPA), 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Council of Agricultural Organizations, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Crop Reporting Service, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Correspondence--D, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Dairy Herd Improvement, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Dairy Program, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Dean's List, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- United States Department of Labor, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- University Development, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Correspondence--E, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Eastern Artificial Insemination Cooperative, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Center for Improvement of Undergraduate Education, includes final report "Evaluation of Undergraduate, Problem-Oriented, Interdisciplinary, Team-Taught Courses in International Studies", 1974 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Education Department, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 23-24)
- Office of Education Development, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Education--Higher Act Title I (Continuing Education), 1973 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Empire State Farm Days, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Energy, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Enrollments, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Department of Environmental Conservation, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Environmental Leaders' Forum (H. Everhart. Everhart;--Chrm.), 1974 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Environmental Leaders' Forum III, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Coordinator for Environmental Programs (V. Truscott., 1974 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- Environmental Protection Agency, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- College of Environmental Sciences and Forestry (Syracuse), 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- Environmental Studies Program, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 36-37)
- Environmental Quality, Research and Graduate Education Program on Management of Nutrients to Optimize Environmental Quality, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- Equal Program Opportunity (EPO), 1973 (Box 13, Folder 39-40)
- Ethnic Studies Center, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 41)
- Experimental and Multi-Disciplinary Studies, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 42)
- Correspondence--F, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 43)
- Federal Appropriations, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 44)
- Field Crops Program Suggestions, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 45)
- Fire Blight, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 46)
- Fleet Cars, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 47)
- Fleet Garage, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 48)
- Ford Foundation, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 49)
- Foreign Visitors Information, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 50)
- FTEs, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 51)
- Correspondence--G, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 52)
- General Foods, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 53)
- General Services, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 54)
- Geneva, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 55-57)
- Graduate School, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 58)
- Correspondence--H, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 59)
- Hayes Study, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 60)
- United States Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 61)
- Higher Education, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 62)
- Ho-Nun-De-Kah, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 63)
- Horses, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 64)
- Hudson Valley Fruit Management Specialist, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 65)
- Hudson Valley Lab, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 66)
- Human Affairs Program, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 67-69)
- School of Human Ecology, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 70)
- Correspondence--I, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 71)
- Center of Improvement of Undergraduate Education, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 72)
- New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (ILR), 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 73)
- Internal Study of College, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 74)
- International Rice Research Institute, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 75)
- Council on International Science and Education, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 76)
- International Student Office, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 77)
- Center for International Studies, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 78-79)
- Isles of Shoals, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
- Ithaca College--Cornell Cooperation, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Correspondence--J, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Correspondence--K, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Correspondence--L, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- College Program on Long Island, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- LUNR, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Members of Assembly, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Congressmen, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- County Law 224, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Governor's Office, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Senators, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Legislators' Meeting on Food Prices, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- McConnell, Joseph A., 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Lincoln University of Missouri--Cooperative Extension and Cooperative Research Divisions, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Correspondence--M, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Management Systems and Analysis, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Medical College, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Migrant, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Milk Marketing Position, 1970-1973 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Miner Institute, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Correspondence--N, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Narcotics, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges (NASULGC)--Division of Agriculture, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 25-26)
- NASULGC--Meeting with Secretary Butz, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- NASULGC--Council of Administrative Heads of Agriculture, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- NASULGC--Division of Agriculture, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 29-31)
- NASULGC--Executive Committee of Division of Agriculture, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 32-33)